<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogues>
	<dialogue id = "-1">
		<intro>
		Steve says "Sarah tells me you've been dragging your feet
		on project Ghoul! Didn't I tell you I want that to be your
		group's number one priority!"
		</intro>
	</dialogue>
        <dialogue id = "1">
		<intro>
		You walk into class, and Steve, the professor, calls you over.			
		"How's it going? Good? Great! Just to let you know, You're
		your new group leader. Don't think it means anything, all it
		means is you're the new group leader. By the way, are you
		ready for your demo today?"

		You still have a few minutes before you have to demo, you
		should get a laptop and use it in this room!
		</intro>
		<cont>
		"Are you ready for your demo?" Steve asks.

		You better find a laptop and use it in this room!
		</cont>
		<condition>TITLE</condition>
		<status>(maybe) Tech Savvy</status>
		<done>
		Due to the fact that you had no idea what you were 
		supposed to be demoing, your demo did not go too well.
		However, your stories miraculously got approved. Now all you
		have to do is turn it in. How hard could that be?
		</done>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "2">
                <intro>
		Steve addresses the whole class now.
		"Ok everyone, do your sprint retrospective and turn in your
		notecards."
	
		Notecards? Forget the retrospective, you had better quickly
		find 5 notecards!
                </intro>
                <cont>
                You don't have your 5 notecards yet, so you probably shouldn't 
		talk to Steve yet.
                </cont>
                <done>
                You got your notecards turned in just before the bell. Now
		for the pull request! You should go talk to your computer in
		your dorm room.
		</done>
		<condition>INVENTORY</condition>
                <status>x5 Notecard</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "4">
                <intro></intro>
                <cont></cont>
                <done>
                "This is unacceptable." Steve says as you walk over.
		"Sarah tells me that your group hasn't been able to meet
		any of the deadlines on the critical path for Project Ghoul.
		What's more, I don't even see any of your features for this
		sprint in the dev branch! What has your group been doing?
		You need to get your priorities straight, and stop holding
		back other groups with your sloppy work!"

		You try to explain how Sarah deleted all your changes for the
		last sprint, but he doesn't seem to believe you. You should
		probably tell the rest of your team what's going on, so they
		can get all the necessary work done.
                </done>
                <condition>SUCCESS</condition>
                <status>null</status>
        </dialogue>
</dialogues>
