<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogues>
        <dialogue id = "-1">
                <intro>
                "Hey now that you're here, we should do a quick daily standup!
		Its really important to function as a team."

		You make a poor excuse, and quickly walk away.
                </intro>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id = "5">
                <intro></intro>
                <cont>
                You talk to Patty, who informs you that the project is going
		south because the different teams have no communication, and
		your own team never does the daily standups. You decide that
		daily standups are unnecessary, but should probably get some
		communiction going with other teams. Sarah is unlikely to
		cooperate, but if you can get Chris to work with you, the
		next merge should be a lot easier. Maybe you could contact
		him over Piazza?
                </cont>
                <done></done>
                <condition>null</condition>
                <status>null</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "8">
		<intro></intro>
		<cont></cont>
		<done>
		You find Patty and summarize your meeting with Erik. You
		leave out the part where you gave a rambling madman 200
		dollars to give you nonsensical advice.

		"A Kanban Board?" Patty asks. "I've heard of them, but never
		seen one! Of course, now that you mention it, that would 
		solve all our problems! Can you get me one? I promise it will
		be worth your time."

		Now you have to find a Kanban Board. I guess you should ask if
		MRP-8 has a spare one...
		</done>
		<condition>SUCCESS</condition>
		<status>null</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "11">
                <intro></intro>
                <cont></cont>
		<done>
		You hand over the Kanban Board to Patty, who excitedly thanks
		you, saying this will finally get the group back on track.

		Congratulations, You've Won! Now you may be asking, what about
		Sarah? Or Steve?
		You can play all of those quest lines and more, all you have
		to do is purchase the $40 dlc expansion pack!
		</done>
                <condition>SWAP</condition>
                <status>1,Kanban Board,Trophy,1,3000,A small shiny trophy,Victorious,1</status>
        </dialogue>
</dialogues>
