<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogues>
        <dialogue id = "-1">
                <intro>
                "Sensei Rother demands the use of the improvement kata to
		balance your constraints and diffuse work through a bill of
		resources, and harness the collective powers of the first and
		second ways in order to procreate synergies and reduce wait
		times!"
                </intro>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id = "7">
		<intro>
		You see a homeless looking man standing by the street. You ask
		if he is the great manager known as Erik.

		"Ah so you've heard of me! Well, I used to give my advice for
		free, but now its going to cost you. Give me 200 dollars and
		I'll consider helping you."

		If you want your group to improve, you have no choice but to
		give him what he wants.
		</intro>
		<cont>
		"Do you have your money yet? No? Well then have fun figuring
		out the sacred scriptures of senseis Allspaw and Goldratt,
		or their holy and venerable three ways!"
                </cont>
		<done>
		You hand over the money. He thanks you, and says he wants to
		take you to a temple known as MRP-8. Talk to him when you're
		ready to go.
		</done>
                <condition>PAY</condition>
                <status>200</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "8">
                <intro>
                Erik drives you to MRP-8, which is much less exciting than the
		temple of divine productivity you were promised. He walks you
		past the security guard, and takes you up above the factory
		floor.

		"What do you see?"

		You give him some wishy washy answer about a bunch of boxes and
		machines.

		"NONSENSE! This is the pinnacle of group evolution! All three
		ways elegantly combined together in an orgasmic display of
		effeciency! The enlightened individuals who run this plant
		understand perfectly the 4 types of work: Planned work, 
	        Internal Improvements, Changes, and Coffee Runs. Normally, I
		would let you figure that out, but that would've taken you a
		month."

		"By using the three ways, the plant managers managed to bring
		together a bunch of unintelligent machines, and can get them
		to work together better than you can get your group of software
		engineers to! How? Simple! Kanban Boards! Always Kanban Boards!
		Sensei Allspaw's teachings about takt time allowed the plant to
		automate manual task, decreasing wait time and leveraging
		synergies. Proactively! That's the key to success in group
		projects!"

		You look at him strangely. "Proactively leverage our
		synergies?" You ask. Erik smacks you on the head in reply.

		"Haven't you heard anything I've said? Kanban Boards! That's
		secret! Leverage those synergies also, and never forget to
		HTML your blockchain into bitcoins, but the secret is Kanban
		Boards!"

		You quickly write that down, and when you look up, Erik is
		gone. I guess you have to find your own way home.
                </intro>
                <cont>
                "Oh you've made it back? Did you think about what I told you?
		It was probably just wasted upon you, you're too thick to
		understand the enlightening principles of the saviors, even
		after I spelled it out for you."
                </cont>
                <done></done>
		<condition>TP1</condition>
                <status>10</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "10">
		<intro>
		You approach Erik and ask that he give you another lesson on
		the scriptures of DevOps. He agrees to do it for free this
		time, as you're a returning customer. You tune out his
		monologue of gibberish this time, and wait until he disappears
		to start looking for a Kanban Board.
		</intro>
		<cont>
		Once again, you ask Erik to take you to MRP-8. He is more
		enthusiastic this time, and seems to believe you are starting
		to get the hang of his teachings.
		</cont>
		<done></done>
		<condition>TP2</condition>
		<status>10</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "11">
                <intro>
		You tell Erik that you finally have a Kanban Board. He
		congradulates you, mumbles something about getting you to
		write a book, and tells you to give it to Patty so you don't
		break it.
                </intro>
                <cont>
                You should give the Kanban Board to Patty like Erik told you.
                </cont>
                <done></done>
                <condition>null</condition>
                <status>null</status>
        </dialogue>

</dialogues>
