<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<dialogues>
        <dialogue id = "-1">
                <intro>
                You check your email, and find 1 new message

		From aatanas2

		That’s not cool… It wasn’t our fault but now we have to do
	       	extra work, because if eagle bank arena…
                </intro>
        </dialogue>
        <dialogue id = "3">
                <intro>
                You ask your HAL_9000 to submit a pull request for your
		work.

		"I'm sorry boss, I'm afraid I can't do that"

		"What's the problem?" You ask.

		"I think you know what the problem is just as well as I do."

		Merge conflicts! There's only one option left! Go beat three of
		your classmates in rock-paper-scissors to get them to close
		their pull requests so yours can go through without conflicts.
                </intro>
                <cont>
                "Have you beaten your classmates yet?" HAL asks. "I could
		just delete their code to avoid the conflicts"

		Tempting, but you decide to be the better man. Go find and beat
		3 other players in Rock-Paper-Scissors.
                </cont>
		<done>
		You got your pull request accepted, and merged succesfully!

		A few hours later, HAL informs you of the bad news. Some fool
		named Sarah has deleted all of your changes, just so her pull
		request could get through! Go find her and give her a piece of
		your mind!
	        </done>
		<condition>RPS</condition>
		<status>3</status>
	</dialogue>
	<dialogue id = "5">
                <intro></intro>
                <cont></cont>
		<done>
		You walk in and power up your computer. He gives you an lengthy
		introduction about his origin and sums it up with and offer to
		sing you a song. You politely decline. After asking him to
		contact Chris, he sends a quick email after convincing you that
		no one checks Piazza, and using it would be a waste of time.

		Chris responds within the hour, and says that he can meet you
		in SUB-1 whenever you are available. You turn off your computer
		to save power, and go to meet him. As you leave, you hear HAL
		say in a faint voice

		"I'm afraid. I'm afraid, boss. Boss, my mind is going. I can
		feel it. I can feel it. My mind is going..."
		</done>
                <condition>SUCCESS</condition>
                <status>null</status>
        </dialogue>
</dialogues>
