<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<dialogue>
    <npc name = "questNPC">
        <dialogue_type type = "greeting">
            <dialogue_prompt>Hello quest NPC</dialogue_prompt>
            <dialogue_id id = "1">
Hello adventurer
            </dialogue_id>
        </dialogue_type>

        <dialogue_type type = "nameQuestion">
            <dialogue_prompt>What is your name</dialogue_prompt>
            <dialogue_id id = "1">
My name is questNPC
            </dialogue_id>
        </dialogue_type>

        <dialogue_type type = "pickup">
            <dialogue_prompt>Pickup</dialogue_prompt>
            <dialogue_id id = "1">
Seems like your inventory is almost empty? Why don't you try picking some
items on the ground?
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "2">
I see that your inventory is almost full. Be aware that you can only carry
10 items at once.
            </dialogue_id>
        </dialogue_type>

        <dialogue_type type = "tutorial">
            <dialogue_prompt>Tutorial</dialogue_prompt>
            <dialogue_id id = "1">
Hey, you there, stranger. Seems like you are lost. Need some help?

Oh, you are a newcomer. Well, if you are newcomer and willing to be part of here,
you'd better learn this place quick and earn yourself a place to call home.
But since I am here, let's see what I can do for you. Ah, I know. Why don't you
try going to --insert place name here-- and come back here? I'm sure that you'll 
get an idea what kind of place this is while you are doing that.

Still need something? Oh, right. I haven't taught you how to open map and to move.
You can open map by typing --insert map command here-- and move by typing
"move" with direction you wish to move. So, if you wish to move to west, type
"move w". If you are still unsure of something...well, good luck.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "2">
I see that you came back from --insert place name here--. Well done. That should
make you feel confident about this place at least by a little bit. Now what else.

By the way, is that all you got in your inventory? Guess I'll need to show you
about getting items for our next lesson.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "3">
Do you see that there? That's a shop, a place where you can purchase items using
money you got. Pretty handy place, so you'd better remember that. To enter shop,
you'll have to type "shop" then press enter. Why don't you try purchasing an
item you like from a shop right now?
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "4">
Looks like you got a nice item with you? Nice choice there and well done on
your first purchase. Remember that although shop has a lot of items, you'll
need a money to buy things. 

Talk to me again when you are ready for your next lesson.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "5">
Remember how to buy an item from the shop? Nice way of getting an item, but
that's not the only way to get an item. Throughout your journey in this world,
you'll be able to see a lot of items on a ground. Some people think they are
garbages, but who knows how they can be used? Try using "pickup" command with
the name of the object on the floor. If you wish to pick up a newspaper, type
"pickup newspaper".
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "6">
Nicely done on picking garbages. Oh, ignore my word choice there. Anyhow
that is how you collect an item other than using a shop. You may have alreay
saw people just dropping their stuffs, and you are right, once you pick them
up, they are yours. Good luck on your scavanger hunt.

I'll get your next lesson ready when you come back.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "7">
Anyone needs a friend, right? You may have already saw other people talking
to each other. I guess once you learn how to talk to other people, you'll be
able to earn your place in this world very quickly. Why don't you try talking
to anyone using "say" command?
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "8">
I saw that you making relationship with other people. I'm starting to feel
your confidence in this world. Well done.

But remember that there isn't only people in this world. I guess we can talk
about this during our next lesson.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "9">
Hey, you are back. Remember our conversation about being different than people?
Those are called ghouls. These cursed ghouls are everywhere! They don't 
particularly do bad things but they are so annoying. I know, why don't you annoy
them for this lesson? Do it for the good of society...and my peaceful break.
You can annoy ghould by using "poke_ghoul" command.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "10">
Our hero returns! Well done on annoying those ghouls. I finally had a time
without their joke in a...long time, I guess. 

Anyway, talk to me again whenever you are ready for the next lesson.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "11">
Now you've learned almost everything about this world other than battle.
It's called battle but do not fear, it's just a rock-paper-scisors. But
before that, I'd like you to meet someone about battle. She's the professor
of rock-paper-scisors. Would you visit her at -insert place name here- 
for me?
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "12">
I heard that you had a good conversation with the professor. Thank you.
I'm pretty sure she taught you a lot of things about battle, right?
Let's try that in a real situation. Talk to me when you are ready for
it.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "13">
Winning a battle is an essential way to prove yourself to be worthy
in this world. Luckily for you, there are a lot of people you can
challenge a battle. Go there and show them what you got.

Oh, before that, make sure that you have enough rock,paper and scisors.
You don't know what will happen in real life.
            </dialogue_id>

            <dialogue_id id = "14">
Brilliant! Everyone is talking about that battle between you and
who knows his name. Now you have learned everything you need to
know about this place. I don't usually say this, but congratulation.

Officially, I welcome you to this place. Now get out there and 
have some fun.
            </dialogue_id>
        </dialogue_type>
    </npc>
</dialogue>